Aviel Yosef

Software Engineer

Contact

Phone 050-9067205

E-mail

Avielyo10@gmail.com

LinkedIn

www.linkedin.com/in/aviely osef

www

https://avielyo10.github.io

Software Engineer with 3 years experience participating in the complete product development lifecycle of successfully launched applications.

Taking an active role on open-source development projects related to CI & DevOps - such as **Jenkins** and **Kafka**.

Team player software engineer with a can-do attitude, phenomenal time management skills, and self-motivated.

For more interesting projects see: https://github.com/Avielyo10

Work History

2021-05 -Current

Software Engineer

Red Hat, Edge Management & Automation

- Working cross teams in order to integrate the FDO (FIDO Device Onboard) process with the Fleet Management team.
- Taking an active role in the development of edgeapi, leading features and improvements to the edge-api core image while reducing its size by 59%~.

2020-08 -2021-05

Associate DevOps Engineer

Red Hat, Telco 5G / Edge

- Design, lead & maintain CNF pipelines flows in 3 telco teams, from e2e.
- Building tools for the teams to use in order to produce a rapid queries regarding
 CPU utilization using Prometheus.

2018-08 -2020-08

CI/DevOps intern

Red Hat, Central CI

- Continuously integrated and deployed developed software. Updated the continuous integration/deployment scripts as necessary to improve continuous integration practices.
- In one of my projects I've managed to improve my team's service by creating a whole new solution using OpenShift & parallel computation making it run 5 times faster using only 25% of the resources than before.
- Built modern applications from scratch using JAVA,
 Kotlin, Python, Groovy & bash.
- Taking a part of the Jenkins code reviewers community.

Education

2017-03 -2020-08

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

Ariel University

- GPA 89.
- Graduated Magna Cum Laude.
- Dean's list, second & third year.
- Within the cyber program the program for outstanding students at Ariel University.
- I've participated in defense and attack cyber laboratories using the university simulator where we get familiar with organizational tools such as ArcSight, Zenoss, VMware vSphere, etc.

2016-03 -2016-12

Technion Certified Security Expert: Computer And Information Systems Security

Technion's Division of Continuing Education

- GPA 100.
- Certified as: MCSA 2012, VMware VCP6, CCNA & CCSA.
- Hands-On course, including network management, virtualization, communication and cybersecurity solutions.